

Danny Blackstock

dannyblackstock.com

❷ dannyblackstock@gmail.com

604 936 6778

profile

I am a multidisciplinary designer and senior student at Simon Fraser University's School of Interactive Art and Technology. I enjoy learning how and why people's everyday experiences can be affected by design, and I have a strong interest in user interface design, web development, and videography.

technical skills

Proficient		Working knowledge	
Photoshop	Flash	PHP	Arduino
Illustrator	HTML + CSS	Javascript	Processing
Indesign	Git	MySQL	After Effects
Premiere	SketchUp	Python	

work experience

User Experience Designer / Developer for Evident Point Software 2013 Evident Point is a small software company developing e-Publishing software.

Roles

- Design user interfaces for an interactive e-book web application, as well as websites, Android, iOS, and Windows applications.
- Create sketches and mockups to communicate how these designs will work and look to clients and development team.
- Produce and implement designs and assets into websites and web applications using HTML, CSS, and SASS, and optimize assets for use in native tablet apps.
- Test and resolve minor bugs in a Javascript web application, while working in a Ruby on Rails environment.

Results

Designs implemented into a web application with thousands of users, as well as native iOS, Android, and Windows applications, and various websites. Communicated with clients successfully to fulfill their needs and requirements.

community involvement

Graphic Designer for Sense Tecnic Systems

2013

Sense Tecnic is a software company developing tools for ubiquitous computing.

Roles

- Design a variety of icons and interface elements for a mobile web application, while being consistent with the client's branding.
- Create mockups to illustrate what the designs would look like to the client.
- Integrate them into the Kurugo mobile web application by generating assets and implementing them using CSS.
- Test the designs on various mobile devices.

Results

Designs used in demo applications for the cities of Richmond and Surrey, BC.



community involvement Technology Coordinator for Enactus Simon Fraser

2012-2014

Enactus SFU is an organization that uses entreprenuerial projects to address the social, environmental, and economic needs in the community.

Roles

- · Maintain and enhance the user experience of Enactus SFU's various websites, through interface design, as well as HTML, CSS, and WordPress customization.
- · Shoot, edit and compile video, images, and audio of Enactus events and causes.
- · Create motion graphics in After Effects to enhance the message of the videos.
- · Collaborate and communicate effectively with different teams in order to complete cohesive video projects for their needs.

Results

Created a event commercial shown on national television, produced videos that were used in competitions with other university Enactus groups, as well as presentations to Simon Fraser University's faculty and students.

Graphic Designer for MADRenegade

2011-2012

MADrenegade, or Media Advertising and Design by Renegade, was a small creative organization run by Students in Free Enterprise SFU, now called Enactus SFU.

Roles

- Conceptualize, sketch, and create ogos for fellow SFU student projects.
- · Communicated with these students in order to produce and deliver work that is tailored for them and leaves them satisfied.

Results

Logo designs were used by senior business students in their academic projects.

awards

President's Honour Roll

Achieved a term GPA of 4.0 or above while enrolled in at least 12 units of classes.

Seattle Design Charette Fall 2012

Part of the winning team of a three day spatial / architectural design competition.

Simon Fraser University Summit Entrance Scholarship

Grade 12 average greater than 90%.

Media Arts 12 Scholarship

Awarded for receiving the highest mark in the class.

education

Simon Fraser University

2011-Present

School of Interactive Arts & Technology. This program focuses on combining science, art, and technology into the creation of digital and physical systems and effective design.

i also enjoy

Epic hiking adventures, playing drums, cars, skiing, tennis, and rock music (eg. The Strokes, Foals, Tokyo Police Club).